Hey,
you um
you really
you're tall.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, wow. And you're funny, too.
Why did you send Misaki to Overwatch?
>> The agents there will not let him fall
to his demons.
>> Huh. You really have a lot of faith in
them.
>> I do because they never let me fall to
mine.
>> The Hashimoto don't stand a chance now
that we're back together.
Just don't run off on your own again,
okay?
>> I will walk this path by your side,
Pocket Ninja.
I promise.
>> I always see you with that smiling
onion.
>> Yeah,
what about it?
>> Nothing.
I think it's cute.
>> Same.
>> When I visit Genji in Japan, I better
not find him hacked to pieces again.
>> If you do, it will not have been by my
hand.
>> So, you let someone else hack him up
instead?
>> [sighs]
>> That was not what I meant.
>> I'm glad Toshiro is safe now, but I wish
we didn't have to blow up his forge.
>> He'll find a way to keep up his craft.
>> But that building held all his secrets.
>> No, he does.
Isn't that why you guys bothered keeping
him alive?
There was a tea leaf standing up in my
cup this morning. That means good luck,
right?
>> Not if you tell me. Oh, you ruined that
for yourself.
>> When I think of what you put Misaki
through, I feel sick to my stomach.
>> Oh, my little Opachki kun.
You should focus on what he put you
through instead.
>> Keep pushing on, mix around, and the
freaks will be coming for you.
>> Who are you?
>> I'm about to be the thorn in your side,
big boy.
>> That's pig boy to you.
>> Sorry if this is a rude question,
but are Are of feeling regret?
>> I often ponder negative past events I
can no longer change. Does that reflect
the experience accurately?
>> Yeah, I'd say it does.
>> Genji?
You knew the champ?
>> Oh, you mean Hammond? Yes, we were
friends on a lunar colony.
>> Not what he said.
>> Since you're handling Genji now, you
should know that his performance will
suffer if he's cuddled.
>> I don't need him to perform. Overwatch
isn't a circus.
>> [laughter]
>> You could have fooled me.
>> You must be ashamed, losing that boy to
Overwatch. I suppose the Hashimoto do
not value fealty as I do.
>> They can have his loyalty for all I
care. As long as I control his fear,
he's still mine.
>> What's wrong, cowboy? You miss Genji
that bad?
>> [laughter]
>> He ain't the only one. Got a lot of old
friends out there I've been thinking
about lately.
>> You're not trapped here, Cole. I know
you'd be doing good wherever you end up.
>> That makes one of us.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> But not as easy as you'd say.
>> Funny that guys with no loyalties keep
ending up at Overwatch.
>> Guys?
You mean it's not just me?
>> Oh, did I say that? Slip of the tongue.
>> Genji made a strong case for you,
recruit. Don't let him down.
>> I won't.
Not when you're all giving me another
chance at life.
>> Why have you forsaken me? I taught you
strength. I gave you a reason to live.
>> No, Toshiro san in the Yakuza did.
>> You think they still care for you after
what you did?
It's not too late to return to my side.
>> Never. I made my choice, and it wasn't
you.
>> Of all your queens' pawns, you seem the
most cutthroat.
>> I ain't her pawn.
>> Perhaps not, but she plays you all the
same.
>> You and old Mako seem to be having a
good time out here. Enjoying the
Pachimaris.
>> That we are. The sound of those sweet
little onions are a sonorous symphony to
my eardrums.
>> Like when you squeeze them?
>> No. Like when we bomb the whole machine.